<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Initiatives on Become | Starting and Sustaining Initiatives that Grow God&#39;s Kingdom.</title>
    <link>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Initiatives on Become | Starting and Sustaining Initiatives that Grow God&#39;s Kingdom.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 17:51:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slam</title>
      <link>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/slam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 17:51:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/slam/</guid>
      <description>Overview SLAM is a Metro Detroit artist collective united by a common dream to end prejudice in our region. The chief goal of SLAM is to invite people into lifelong, cross-cultural friendships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Sea</title>
      <link>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/kingdomsea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 17:49:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/kingdomsea/</guid>
      <description>Overview Founded in 2018, Kingdom Sea aims to help introduce people to Jesus by praying for them, connecting in friendship, sharing life and faith, and finally empowering them to make disciples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivate</title>
      <link>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/cultivate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:47:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/cultivate/</guid>
      <description>Overview As defined by Jesus in Luke 10, a kingdom worker is a person of Christlike character - obedient to God, ready for any challenge, action-minded, and results-oriented - whose desire is to see God’s Kingdom grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Oasis</title>
      <link>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/internationaloasis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youwillbecome.org/initiatives/internationaloasis/</guid>
      <description>Overview International Oasis exists to inspire and equip international students to meet the needs of the global poor. International Oasis believes that international students hold the solutions to the problems of poverty in their home countries because international students who come to the United States are generally people with strong personal character, relational networks, and intellect who demonstrate perseverance in the face of challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>